FABIOLA FARIA

fabiolacezarfaria@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/ffabiola/ | github.com/fabicf

SUMMARY

Motivated Software Developer, with a Science Background, who enjoys learning and discover new skills. My previous non-IT experiences have allowed me to develop analytical skills, attention to detail, customer service, teamwork and problem solving, which combined with my IT skills acquired in college, could be a perfect fit for a software developer position.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Front-end: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, React, Ajax, jQuery Back-end: C# .NET, WPF, XAML, Java, NodeJS, REST API, PHP

Database: SQL, MySQL, SQL Server

Tools: Git, Jira, GitLab, Bitbucket, Balsamiq Wireframe, Trello, MS Office Miscellaneous: OOP, Agile/Scrum Methodology, WMS, ERP, CRM, ImageJ

EDUCATION

John Abbott College - Montreal QC Internet Programming and Development, 2020 – 2021 (Graduating in July 2021) Attestation of College Studies

State University of Western Paraná - Toledo (Brazil)

BSc. /Teaching License - Chemistry, 2016

EXPERIENCE

Shipping Coordinator

Allied International Pipes and Fittings, Montreal QC, May 2020 - Oct 2020

Customer Service arranging pickups, order entry, processing of inventory receipts for inbound stock. Issuing of product certification, daily updating of inventory in the company WMS and office related tasks.

Shipping and Receiving Coordinator

Town and Country Living, Montreal QC, Jun 2019 - Feb 2020

Responsible for cross-border shipping documents and phone/email support for national and international customers including the largest clothing retail company in the US. Processing of orders and office related tasks (scanning, photocopies, filling documentation, e-mail and phone support, Outlook, MS Office, etc.).

Previous Experiences

Brazil 2016 - 2018

Worked as chemist researcher after graduate, and as a High School and College Teacher for the Government of Brazil.

AWARDS AND HOUNOURS

Dean's List - Fall 2020 Semester/John Abbott College

The Dean's List recognizes the achievement of full-time students who have earned an average of 80% or more for the semester.

ELAP Emerging Leaders of America Program - Canadian Government Award, 2017

One of 400 students from all over Latin America selected for a 6-months research in a Canadian university (Concordia/McGill – Sep 2017 – Mar 2018).